Melissa’s vacation just turned into a rescue mission.
Dadnapped is a comedy, adventure, action film directed by Paul Hoen.
Melissa has a bad case of sibling rivalry, only her competition is a fictional
character in her father's best-selling novel about a teenage super spy.
When her father is "dadnapped" by a group of overzealous fans, it's up
to Melissa to help him by tapping her inner superhero.
Melissa Morris, played by Emily Osment.
Wheeze, played by David Henrie.
Merv Kilbo, played by Jason Earles.
Neal Morris, played by George Newbern.
Maurice Legarche, played by Phill Lewis.
Debbie, played by Jennifer Stone.
Dadnapped is a 2009 American crime comedy film
released as a Disney Channel Original Movie.
It premiered February 16, 2009.
Starring actors from Disney Channel Original Series, the
movie had 4.6 million viewers for its premiere.
Although the story centers on a hostage situation, the kidnappers are
inept and the film "practically oozes kid-pleasing content".
The tone is lighthearted.